the most
important
ingredient yes
hard work is there
dedication is
there passion is
there but I felt
being honest is
one of the most
important thing be
to start of being
honest to yourself
unless you are
you can't be
honest to others
hi ever met
someone who speaks
their mind
honestly without
any filters that's
called candor
candor it's about
being open
truthful and
straightforward in
what you said
imagine you're
giving feedback to
a friend candor is
when you are
honest but
respectful sharing
your thoughts
without
sugarcoating
things it's
honesty at your
best so the next
time when you're
honest remember
the word candor